<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Obey the Testing Goat!</title><link href="http://www.obeythetestinggoat.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://www.obeythetestinggoat.com/feeds/all-en.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://www.obeythetestinggoat.com/</id><updated>2013-03-26T18:35:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>"Test Driven Development of Web Applications" -- the book exists, and is available on Early Release</title><link href="http://www.obeythetestinggoat.com/tdd-web-programming-book-on-oreilly-early-release.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-26T18:35:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Harry</name></author><id>tag:www.obeythetestinggoat.com,2013-03-26:tdd-web-programming-book-on-oreilly-early-release.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Front cover of book" src="/static/images/front_cover_screenshot.png" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can't quite believe this is actually happening, but I have not only signed a contract with O'Reilly, but i have actually written the first four chapters, or at least a first draft of the first four chapters!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For anyone new, the idea is to provide an introduction to TDD for web app development, for beginners -- whether it's people who've never done web development and Django before, or just people who've never done TDD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm releasing the book as early as possible to try and gather feedback, so please, please do get yourself a copy, and tell me what I'm doing right and wrong!  What would you change?  Am I pitching it at the right level?  Is the pace right or wrong? Should I spend more or less time on explaining the basics of Django, more or less time on the basics of TDD, more or less time with detailed examples?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the book on the O'Reilly Early Release program:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kqzyfj.com/click-7079286-11260198?url=http%3A%2F%2Fshop.oreilly.com%2Fproduct%2F0636920029533.do%3Fcmp%3Daf-code-book-product_cj_9781449367794_%7BPID%7D&amp;cjsku=0636920029533" target="_top"&gt;
Test-Driven Development with Python&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.awltovhc.com/image-7079286-11260198" width="1" height="1" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buying direct from O'Reilly is probably the best option, they have DRM-free versions you can download in all sorts of formats (MOBI/epub/pdf)...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, if you have an account on Safari, you can &lt;a href="http://my.safaribooksonline.com/9781449365141"&gt;get it there too&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, this is an early draft, so expect the occasional rough edges... But I really, really want your feedback folks, so do let me know what you think -- here in the comments, in the comments on either site, or just by email to &lt;a href="mailto:hjwp2@cantab.net"&gt;hjwp2@cantab.net&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone for your kind words of support, and thanks in advance for your help!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[update] -- in case it's not clear:  if you buy this book now, either via O'Reilly or via Safari, you'll get updates from now on, as each new chapter is released, until the final version is released and you get the full copy.  Anyone that provides feedback is totes getting a credit in the final book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[update 2] -- &lt;em&gt;naturally&lt;/em&gt; I assume you're all more than keen to &lt;strong&gt;pay&lt;/strong&gt; for this book, but just as a matter of principle, there will be a Creative Commons, "try-before-you-buy", free version of the early drafts, released sometime in the near future.  The final version of the book will also have a Creative Commons (NC-ND) digital version released on publication.  And after 10 years, it will automatically revert to CC-0 Public Domain. But I (and my publishers) very much appreciate every single early sale!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[update 3] -- follow me on twitter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hjwp"&gt;@hjwp&lt;/a&gt; or sign up for this blog's updates to find out more about progress with the book, including when the CC version comes out... And, just let me know you're interested!&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="book"></category><category term="O'Reilly"></category><category term="Early Release"></category></entry><entry><title>The next stage: writing a book</title><link href="http://www.obeythetestinggoat.com/writing-a-book-announcement.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Harry</name></author><id>tag:www.obeythetestinggoat.com,2013-01-08:writing-a-book-announcement.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've decided to try and develop this tutorial into an actual book on test-driven development for web apps.  Have a look at the chapter outline I've posted as part 6:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.tdd-django-tutorial.com/tutorial/6/"&gt;http://www.tdd-django-tutorial.com/tutorial/6/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd love to hear what you think!  Am I completely mad?&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="tdd"></category><category term="book"></category></entry></feed>